COREY NANCE

Salem, NH 03079 | EMAIL-COREYNANCE83@GMAIL.COM | 781-426-1186

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/corey-nance-87139841

GitHub: https://github.com/coreyNance

Portfolio: https://coreynance.github.io/Portfolio/

OBJECTIVE

Previous car sales consultant for a little over 13 years, high level of success by maintaining a perfect 100 customer satisfaction score while averaging 25 car sales a month. These achievements allowed me to make the top 100 sales consultant list in the Northeast Business Center. Next family-oriented move, to be a Motor Coach driver for a little over 3 years. While on this job I received countless praise for my professionalism with riders and my camaraderie with co-workers. These achievements attributed to the company's consideration for an Operations Manager Position within that short time. All while attending school at SNHU to get my bachelor's degree in Software Engineering which I currently maintain a GPA of 3.96 and attend UNH's Coding Bootcamp for software development.

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

- Automotive mechanics as a hobby
- Extensive Sales experience
- Extensive Product Knowledge in the automotive field
- Great Customer Service
- Entry level C++
- Entry level Java
- Entry level Python
- Entry level JavaScript
- Entry level HTML/CSS

PROJECTS

- Car Enthusiast Quiz

A program created as a car quiz where user clicks a start button, timer starts. Then user answers presented questions. Time is deducted for wrong answers and high scores are saved and can be cleared. HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Local storage was used for this assignment. https://coreynance.github.io/Car Enthusiast Quiz/

- Daily Planner

Create a simple calendar application that allows a user to save events for each hour of the day. This app runs in the browser and features dynamically updated HTML and CSS powered by jQuery. Moment.js library is used for the date and time. https://coreynance.github.io/Daily_Planner/

Find Me Food Application (Group Project)

The Find Me Food app pulls the user's location immediately from their IP address and feeds it into Google Maps to populate a list of nearby restaurants. The app also has the ability to display a list of restaurants near an alternate zip code, as well as to filter by type of cuisine. https://unh-bootcamp-projects.github.io/project-1-group-c/

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Present

Southern New Hampshire University Manchester, NH

GPA: 4.0

Coding Bootcamp for Full Stack Software Development

Present

Sep 2016 - Sep 2016

University of New Hampshire Portsmouth, NH

• Grade A+

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Motor Coach Driver

Boston Express Bus Londonderry, NH

• To inspect and operate a Motor Coach in the safest manner With up to 51 passengers on board

Sales Consultant Jan 2016 - Sep 2016

Clark Chrysler Jeep Dodge Ram Methuen, MA

• Had the opportunity to become a Motor Coach Driver

Service Advisor Aug 2012 - Nov 2012

Lawless Dodge Chrysler Jeep Woburn, MA

• Help customers through getting their cars fixed in a professional

Sales Consultant Oct 2007 - Aug 2012

Kelly Jeep Chrysler Lynnfield, MA

• Help customers obtain the right vehicle for their needs

Owner Operator Apr 2015 - Jan 2016

Auto quip of New England Salem, NH

• Business Partner